(Howard:)...by, like, a gazillion angry Mexicans.
All right, let me put it this way.
Your gross receipts on this one order...
(Sheldon:)...will be over $3000
for one night's work.
(Penny:)You guys get started.
- What are you doing?
- Going online to buy shoes.
[SINGING]
She'll be coming 'round the mountain
- When she comes
When she comes
PENNY:
SHELDON:
She'll be coming 'round the mountain
BOTH:
(Raj:)If I wanted to spend
my Saturday nights doing this...
(Raj:)...I could have stayed in India.
Oh, stop with the fake third-world crap.
Your father's a gynecologist
and you had a house full of servants.
(Raj:)We only had four servants.
And two of them were children.
(Leonard:)How are we doing?
(Raj:)We have 128 assorted Penny Blossoms
ready to ship.
(Howard:)God, we're never gonna finish in time.